// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question:"Choose the synonym for 'Benevolent':",
    answer: "Kind-hearted",
    options: [
      "Malevolent",
      "Kind-hearted",
      "Hostile",
      "Cruel"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Choose the antonym for 'Ponder'",
    answer: "Disregard",
    options: [
      "Consider",
      "Alan",
      "Reflect",
      "Disregard"
      
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "In which sentence is the word 'Eloquent' used correctly?",
    answer: "She gave an eloquent speech at the event.",
    options: [
      "She gave an eloquent speech at the event.",
      "He was eloquent about his lack of interest in the subject.",
      "The novel had an eloquent plot twist.",
      "His eloquent skills were evident in his musical performance."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Choose the synonym for 'Voracious'",
    answer: "Gluttonous",
    options: [
      "Indifferent",
      "Gluttonous",
      "Abstemious",
      "Abstemious",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Choose the antonym for 'Apathy':",
    answer: "Empathy",
    options: [
      "Empathy",
      "Sympathy",
      "Indifference",
      "Compassion"
    ]
  },
  

     {
   numb: 6,
   question: "In which sentence is the word 'Ubiquitous' used correctly?",
    answer: "The smell of fresh flowers was ubiquitous in the garden",
    options: [
      "The smell of fresh flowers was ubiquitous in the garden",
      "He was puzzled by the ubiquitous riddle.",
      "Ubiquitous people tend to stand out in a crowd.",
      "The cake had a ubiquitous taste that everyone loved."
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Choose the synonym for 'Mellifluous':",
     answer: "Sweet-sounding",
     options: [
       "Harsh",
       "Sweet-sounding",
       "Bitter",
       "Discordant"
     ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "Five friends - George, Helen, Ian, James, and Kate - have different pets: Cat, Dog, Fish, Rabbit, and Turtle. Who has a Cat?",
       answer:"George",
       options: [
         "George" ,
         "Helen",
         "Ian",
         "James"
       ]
      },
      {
        numb: 9,
        question: "In which sentence is the word 'Ephemeral' used correctly?",
         answer: "Her ephemeral interest in painting faded quickly.",
         options: [
           "Her ephemeral interest in painting faded quickly.",
           "The mountain had an ephemeral height that astonished everyone.",
           "The movie had an ephemeral storyline.",
           "His ephemeral personality made him stand out in the group."
         ]
        },
        {
          numb: 10,
          question: "Choose the synonym for 'Pernicious':",
          answer: "Harmful",
          options: [
            "Harmful",
            "Beneficial",
            "Caring",
            "Caring"
          ]
          }
];